Hey it's me and I have a new brand I want to show you. It's Mr. J Cosplay and Costumes
and I got a wide selection today. I have this white and blue sportswear swimwear outfit.
I don't know. This spandex bodysuit and also a black cosplay catsuit which has amazing fabric
but also part of this outfit are cat ears so I'm really looking forward to
all the outfits let's go all right part one of this outfit is this bodysuit and
these stay ups I kind of like the cut with the mesh part here but there's also
this jacket which I think is essential because that elevates the whole outfit
yeah as I thought this is really cool because now we have the loose oversized
top part and this neck bottom part and I do have some white heels. Haha. There we go.
The whole outfit. I'm wearing tights underneath because in my last video with
the bodysuit you to reflect at 18 plus and I think partially because of the
high cut in the legs and I don't know too much skin whatever so thanks YouTube
for nothing I think it's a very cute outfit I especially picked this because
I wanted to show and see something different not just something black not
just a pink catsuit but a completely different style it gives sporty wives
with the stripes here and we all think of Adidas but I also love the cut here
and the design part of the leg here the mesh and how it looks from the back side
I think it's a very nice design dirty take okay dirty take here I wear a size
large in every outfit. The sizing is Asian so please check the sizing charts.
As you see you have to size up basically but the shop is from Canada and I had a
lovely contact with them, great customer service, a huge range of products so if
you're looking for some fun costumes check them out. I'll link it of course in
the description text. But I do love black so I'm going to change into this catsuit
now. The second outfit is this tactical catsuit and part of this outfit are the
ears. They have the same print than the pasties and the bodysuit itself. So, I'm going to put them on.
How does it look?
Oh, they're big.
Like really huge ears.
Anime ears.
I'm not sure how the ears relate to the bodysuit or part of the outfit.
Because this is not a bunny suit or something.
But yeah, it is a catsuit, so why not cat ears?
It's because of the catsuit, you know.
anyway I love the combination here of this stretchy PU fabric and the mesh I
think it's a very nice design also with these kind of rivets in the back and we
do have a cross zipper here which is really handy because I'm wearing
underwear because we're on YouTube and we have these reflective reflective
stripes which adds to the tactical part. It's quite comfy since the pebricks are
really stretchy and again I like the design. I do have this catsuit as a
bodysuit too. I'm going to put this one on next so you have the direct comparison.
you